today i will not sell brownie
and yet I'll make customers buy bro
I never doubt
like I tried hard to be the way she
that they need us
this part of the sale is called follow up
bro what are you doing now brother
leave the brownies in place
people already know my product
then I come giving a silly one
and then man
all right
Liked brownie
the girls loved it you ate
because the feeling I
me and she ate fucking
the noise is good hein bonzão
congratulations
first you conquer
then send the account
we put them there
okay can you say
pô tá
it's really
continues
how much do you need
what is your order
fifty units
sixteen reais each unit
how much do you want
I just closed 1 order out of 200
Charlie Brown
who said they need
today i'm spending the day like this
bro having a cup of coffee
playing idea with sharks
I will talk business
packager
is on
it's another time here now
Juliana
I came here or exchange 1 idea
is closed
hello brother
nicest guy here from Santos
attention brother
having a cup of coffee
not today
today I think he made a way out
then sorted out a few things
particular that he arrived from a trip
talk to the guy
he is not here
but things happen that way
already to exchange an idea with Dani right
it's six o'clock
only six hours here
and I can't put it because of just that
that's all produced here man
brother but bro
thank you very much
not good
sometimes you will get the feedback
and it doesn't mean your product is bad
happened now the guy
he liked my cool product
because we already make the brownie and that's right
is on
slowly we are conquering territory
it's not from night to day
it's a lot of point of sale
turned on
if you call you are making a relationship with the locals
the soft mine unrolled here
already gave me a viewfinder of who owns the stop
talk to this guy here we're going to march
even gave me a Red Bull here
the mother wants to have a coffee
can be a red bull bro
caramba
crazy let's go let's go
on demand has already been created
but I noticed that there's one stop left
it turns out that this video lasts only three minutes
and then it ends
that the algorithm does not deliver
is as follows
guys you noticed